{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather study than ___ to such a place.",
            "a": "to go",
            "b": "go",
            "c": "going",
            "d": "have gone",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Would rather do something than do something ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "On my way home I stopped ___ some bread at the bakery.",
            "a": "buying",
            "b": "to buying",
            "c": "to have bought",
            "d": "to buy",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Stop + V_ing: Don't continue doing something \n- Stop + To Verb: stop (doing) something to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog needs ___.",
            "a": "to train",
            "b": "train",
            "c": "to be trained",
            "d": "to have trained",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- Need + To be Past Particple/ V_ing: if before \"need\" is not person or animal \n- Need + To Verb: If before \"need\" is person or animal \n- Passive voice",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She isn't rich enough ___ the piano, let alone buy it.",
            "a": "rent",
            "b": "renting",
            "c": "to rent",
            "d": "to be rented",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Adjective + enough + to V",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers accepted the cut in salary without complaint because they were afraid ___ their jobs.",
            "a": "to lose",
            "b": "to be lost",
            "c": "to have lost",
            "d": "lose",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Be afraid to do something \n- Tense: past simple tense",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is sometimes difficult ___ you have just met.",
            "a": "to make pleasant conversation among people",
            "b": "making pleasant conversation to people",
            "c": "making pleasant conversation to for people",
            "d": "to make pleasant conversation with people",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- It's difficult (for somebody) to do something \n- Make conversation with someone: talk to someone in order to be polite",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Almost everyone fails ___ the driver's test on the 1st try .",
            "a": "passing",
            "b": "to have passed",
            "c": "to pass",
            "d": "in passing",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Fail + To Verb \n- Tense: simple present",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "When inflation is rampant, many families find it difficult ___ the life style to which they are accustomed.",
            "a": "to maintaining",
            "b": "to maintain",
            "c": "in maintaining",
            "d": "maintain",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Find it difficult to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has no alternative but _________him.",
            "a": "to see",
            "b": "seeing",
            "c": "going to see",
            "d": "see",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Have no choice/alternative + but + To V ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I never know _________ when I go on a trip.",
            "a": "what clothes should be take",
            "b": "what clothes to take",
            "c": "what clothes will I take",
            "d": "I take what clothes",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "- Some verbs: ask, decide, explain, forget, know, show, tell, understand, can be followed by a question word such as where/ how/ what/ who/ when or whether + To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "3",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}